I'm in the Seals Show.
Talking about our group chat topic of the week.
Would you jump in for a friend or a family member if it was getting mollywhopped?
I'm that person I'm going to tell you to start one time and then if they don't break it up,
I'm switching out my heels for my chuck.
We splitting wigs.
We pushing them all the way back past the widow's peak.
Yeah, I'm jumping in. I'm helping.
So listen, I remember being at a club in Texas and my homegirl Ashley Hen was like,
there was these chicks in the club that just kept like circling me.
I don't know why, but they just like kept circling me.
And then finally they just like stepped to me and was like, we got a problem with you.
And Ashley stepped in and was like, what kind of problem you got?
And I was like, oh, this is happening.
And then I looked down. Ashley had on Chucks.
We didn't arrive. We didn't arrive with Ashley and Chucks.
Ashley had peeped them circling at me, went out and changed her shoes
in anticipation of what was going to take place.
So the summation is that y'all are jumping in if someone's getting jumped.
But if it's a one-on-one, people got to take their L's and you'll be there,
I guess, to scoop them up off the pavement, to scrape them up off the pavement.
Like a real friend or family member would do.
Yes.